const localTalentEasyQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is a note?',
    answers: [
      'An instrument',
      'A combination of tones made by an instrument',
      'A single tone made by an instrument',
    ],
    correct: 'A single tone made by an instrument',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Which is not a note?',
    answers: ['C', 'H', 'G'],
    correct: 'H',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'How many strings are on the average guitar?',
    answers: ['6', '5', '7'],
    correct: '6',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'Which genre came first?',
    answers: ['Rock', 'Blues', 'Classical'],
    correct: 'Classical',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'Guitar is classified as which type of instrument?',
    answers: ['Wind', 'String', 'Mood'],
    correct: 'String',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'What is not considered a type of guitar?',
    answers: ['Electric', 'Brass', 'Acoustic'],
    correct: 'Brass',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'What are the knobs at the top of a guitar neck for?',
    answers: ['Exercising fingers', 'Playing notes', 'Tuning'],
    correct: 'Tuning',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'What is an amp?',
    answers: ['Energy drink', 'Amplifier', 'A type of note'],
    correct: 'Amplifier',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'Which type of guitar typically needs an amp?',
    answers: ['Steel', 'Electric', 'Acoustic'],
    correct: 'Electric',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'Where do you put your fingers on a guitar to play notes?',
    answers: ['The body', 'The sound hole', 'The frets'],
    correct: 'The frets',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'Where does the body of a guitar rest?',
    answers: ['The floor', 'Your hand', 'Your leg'],
    correct: 'Your leg',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'Is mayonnaise an instrument?',
    answers: ['Yes', 'No', 'Maybe'],
    correct: 'No',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: 'What are the names of the strings on a guitar?',
    answers: ['E, A, D, G, B, E', 'A, B, C, D, E, F', 'F, E, G, B, A, B'],
    correct: 'E, A, D, G, B, E',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: 'What is the ideal way to place your fingers on strings?',
    answers: ['Completely flat', 'On your fingertips', 'On your knuckles'],
    correct: 'On your fingertips',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: 'Where does the sound resonate from on an acoustic guitar?',
    answers: ['The body', 'The neck', 'The tuning pegs'],
    correct: 'The body',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: 'What symbol tells you to play something over again?',
    answers: ['Andante', 'A treble clef', 'The repeat sign'],
    correct: 'The repeat sign',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: 'Two instruments playing together is called a...',
    answers: ['Combo', 'Duo', 'Duet'],
    correct: 'Duet',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: 'Which of these is not a note?',
    answers: ['E', 'H', 'C'],
    correct: 'H',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: 'Which of these is not a chord?',
    answers: ['E', 'C', 'E-'],
    correct: 'E-',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: 'Which is the highest toned string?',
    answers: ['High E', 'B', 'Low E'],
    correct: 'High E',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: 'What is the thickest string?',
    answers: ['B', 'Low E', 'High E'],
    correct: 'Low E',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: 'Which chord sounds more “sad”?',
    answers: ['Major', 'Maja', 'Minor'],
    correct: 'Minor',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 54,
    question: 'Is a sharp note up or down a fret?',
    answers: ['Up', 'Down', "Neither, it's up one string"],
    correct: 'Up',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 55,
    question: 'Which technique is most commonly used for classical guitar?',
    answers: ['Pick', 'Finger-picking', 'Plucking'],
    correct: 'Finger-picking',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 56,
    question: 'Does a minor scale sound "bright"?',
    answers: ['Yes', 'No', 'Sometimes'],
    correct: 'No',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 57,
    question: 'The thicker the string, the lower the note. True or False?',
    answers: ['True', 'False', 'Depends'],
    correct: 'True',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 58,
    question: 'Would an Em chord sound happy?',
    answers: ['Yes', 'No', 'Sometimes'],
    correct: 'No',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 59,
    question: 'Would an E chord sound happy?',
    answers: ['Yes', 'No', 'Sometimes'],
    correct: 'Yes',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 60,
    question: 'Would a D chord sound happy?',
    answers: ['Yes', 'No', 'Sometimes'],
    correct: 'Yes',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 61,
    question: 'What is a fret?',
    answers: [
      'A type of string',
      'Metal pieces on the neck',
      'The act of worrying about something',
    ],
    correct: 'Metal pieces on the neck',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 62,
    question: 'What is a capo?',
    answers: [
      'A slang term for “cool”',
      'A device to change the guitar’s pitch',
      'A term in music used to say “slow”',
    ],
    correct: 'A device to change the guitar’s pitch',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 63,
    question: 'What is finger picking?',
    answers: [
      'Using a pick to strum the strings',
      'Using your fingers to strum the strings',
      'Using your fingers to pluck the strings',
    ],
    correct: 'Using your fingers to pluck the strings',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 64,
    question: 'Which note comes after F?',
    answers: ['F#', 'G', 'A'],
    correct: 'F#',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    reward: 1,
  },
]

export { localTalentEasyQuestions }
